newbusiness.co.uk 2010-11-21

# Business Advice for business startups, SMEs and Entrepreneurs | NewBusiness Magazine

**1\. Introduction**

newbusiness.co.uk is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. This company wide Online Privacy Policy discloses the information practices for newbusiness.co.uk on the Web. 

The newbusiness.co.uk Website (the "Site") acts as a repository for up to date business news, information and resources. Due to the nature of the business conducted by the site we require you to submit your personal information in order to provide services. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully before you use newbusiness.co.uk. The application of this Privacy Policy is only to newbusiness.co.uk and not to web sites controlled by other companies or organisations we link to. 

**2\. Collection of information**

Information we collect 

(1) Non-personally identifiable information 

When you visit one of our web sites, we may store some information on your computer's hard drive in the form of a "Cookie". Cookies are text files that identify your computer to our server and do not collect any personal information in themselves. We may use cookies to serve you better and more efficiently, and to personalize your experience at our Site. To do so, the cookies we use may record non-personally identifiable information pertaining to your preferences for viewing particular web pages. We may also use cookies to collect non-personally identifiable information to help us in analyzing trends, tracking user's movement, and gathering broad demographic information for aggregate use. 

(2) Personally identifiable information   
In order to provide you with the most fast, efficient and accurate service possible, newbusiness.co.uk requires the collection of certain personally identifiable information. This information is usually restricted to our registration process. The information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services. 

**3\. Access to personal information and Security of personal information**

How does newbusiness.co.uk protect consumer information? 

newbusiness.co.uk takes significant steps to protect your personally identifiable information with secure servers. Any information you provide us is maintained and accessible only by newbusiness.co.uk. 

Third Party Partners 

newbusiness.co.uk may work with other companies to provide offers and promotions that may be of interest to you. You will only receive notification of these offers if you have indicated your willingness to be contacted for such purposes. In these cases, your data remains secure with us. newbusiness.co.uk will not sell or loan your data to third parties nor will any of the third parties be allowed access to your data. 

**4\. Children's information**

While newbusiness.co.uk publish few contents that are targeted directly at children, we are committed to comply with applicable laws and requirements. Children without the consent of their parent or guardian should submit no personally identifiable information to the newbusiness.co.uk web site. newbusiness.co.uk will not knowingly collect from or use any personally identifiable information of children for any purpose, including disclosure to third parties. 

**5\. Europe's data protection**

Because newbusiness.co.uk operates globally, we make information we collect available to our worldwide business units. For those of you visiting us from the European Economic Area, please note that newbusiness.co.uk will transfer your personally identifiable data outside the European Economic Area for use for any of the purposes described above. By using our web site and providing us with your personal data, you consent to such transfer of your personal data. 

**6\. Contact Information**

Comments and questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to [info@newbusiness.co.uk](mailto:info@newbusiness.co.uk)
